For honor. For love. For redemption.
Need for Speed is a action, crime, drama film directed by Scott Waugh.
The film revolves around a local street-racer who partners with a rich and arrogant business
associate, only to find himself framed by his colleague and sent to prison.
After he gets out, he joins a New York-to-Los Angeles race to get revenge.
But when the ex-partner learns of the scheme, he puts a massive bounty on the racer's head, forcing him
to run a cross-country gauntlet of illegal racers in all manner of supercharged vehicles.
Tobey Marshall, played by Aaron Paul.
Dino Brewster, played by Dominic Cooper.
Julia Maddon, played by Imogen Poots.
Benny Jackson, played by Kid Cudi.
Finn, played by Rami Malek.
Joe Peck, played by Ramón Rodríguez.
Need for Speed is a 2014 action crime film based on the racing video game series, directed by Scott Waugh, and
starring Aaron Paul, Dominic Cooper, Scott Mescudi, Imogen Poots, Ramón Rodríguez and Michael Keaton.
It tells the story of street racer Tobey Marshall, who sets off to race cross-country as a way
of avenging his friend's death at the hands of a rival racer, Dino Brewster.
The film received negative reviews, and although it was a box-office disappointment in the United States, it performed
better internationally, grossing $203 million worldwide against a production budget of $66 million.
The film explores themes of competition, street race,
money, super speed, based on video game.
The tone is emotional and intense.